shoprite.com 2016-04-16

# ShopRite Privacy Policy - ShopRite

**At ShopRite, Your Privacy is Our Priority!**

Wakefern Food Corp./ShopRite is committed to protecting the privacy of our customers

* * *

This Privacy Policy is a part of the Terms & Conditions of this website (the “Website”) which are binding on all Website users and participants in the ShopRite® Price Plus® Club. The ShopRite®, ShopRite Partners in Caring®, Price Rite®, and Wakefern Food Corp. websites are operated by MyWebGrocer on behalf of Wakefern Food Corp. (“Wakefern”). Please review MyWebGrocer’s privacy policy posted at [********http://www.shoprite.com/mywebgrocer-privacy-policy/********](http://www.shoprite.com/mywebgrocer-privacy-policy/) to understand how your information is collected and used by MyWebGrocer on our sites. Please also review the privacy policy of Third Solutions LLC, which maintains and operates the digital receipts service available to ShopRite® Price Plus® Club participants at [**https://shoprite.myreceipts.com**](https://shoprite.myreceipts.com/)

Wakefern’s policy is to respect and protect your privacy. Wakefern therefore exercises precautions to maintain the confidentiality of information that you provide to us.

We may gather certain types of personally identifiable information, such as your name, e-mail address, street address or other postal mailing address, telephone number(s), purchase information and history, and if you request check acceptance privileges at our stores, your checking account number and/or driver’s license number (collectively, “Personal Information”). It is therefore important for you to know how we collect, use, disclose, manage, and store the Personal Information that you may voluntarily provide to us, as well as the information that is collected passively on the Website.

This Privacy Policy sets forth Wakefern’s current policies and practices with respect to Personal Information of Website users and ShopRite Price Plus Club participants. Your continued participation on this Website and in the ShopRite Price Plus Club indicates your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and of the collection, use, disclosure, management and storage of your Personal Information as described below.

**If you have any objections to this Privacy Policy,**  
**you should immediately discontinue**  
**use of the Website.**

ShopRite Price Plus Club participants with objections to this Privacy Policy should follow the procedures set forth in the “Opt-Out Procedures” section below.

**Collection and Use of Information  
**We may collect and use aggregate sales information to analyze sales trends. Aggregated information is not covered by this policy because it does not identify any individuals.

You may browse the Website without providing any Personal Information.

We do not collect Personal Information about you except when you provide it, such as when you:

• use your ShopRite® Price Plus® Club card  
• click “ **CONTACT US** ” on the Website to send us a message  
• order a gift card or a holiday platter  
• sign up to receive e-mails  
• use the Website to create a personal shopping list or save recipes  
• request a rebate  
• enter a sweepstakes  
• use on-line coupons or coupons via your mobile phone  
• use iPhone applications for viewing circulars and managing shopping lists

Wakefern collects information about purchases made in ShopRite stores and on the ShopRite website by ShopRite Price Plus Club members. This information allows us to send coupons and information about special offers that will be of interest to you, and inform you of product safety recalls. In the event of an urgent recall of a product you purchased with your ShopRite Price Plus Club card, when practical, the Personal Information you provide may be used to contact you through an automated telephone messaging system or by other means. Please make sure to tell us if your contact information has changed. We will use reasonable efforts to notify you, but we cannot guarantee that you will receive notification of every recall through our service. [**Click here**](http://www.shoprite.com/product-recalls/) to access information regarding product recalls on our website.

If you place an order through the Website, you will be asked to submit certain Personal Information, including your full name and address, as well as financial information such as your credit card number. This financial information is collected by a third party that is clearly identified. The collection of this financial information is subject to the third party’s privacy policy, so we recommend that you take the time to review that privacy policy.  
Additionally, we may post information about career opportunities on the Website. If you are interested in these opportunities, you can submit an application online. We make reasonable efforts to review the applications in a timely fashion.We will not distribute or share Personal Information submitted in relation to employment with any third party without your consent.

We may use your Personal Information to provide you with coupons, promotions, the products and services you request, and to respond to your suggestions and questions.

We may also use your Personal Information to notify you about new products and features that we think may be of interest to you. We may also use your Personal Information for operational and business purposes, or to find out how we can improve our organization and Website via surveys or online tracking mechanisms. We use aggregate Personal Information collected directly during any registration process and via “cookies” to help us evaluate and modify existing services and features.

**Cookies  
**This Website uss “cookies” to obtain non-Personal Information from online visitors in order to improve their online experience and facilitate their visit within the Website. Cookies are small files stored as text on a computer hard drive. Websites can use cookies to recognize repeat visitors, and track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements. If a visitor does not want information collected through the use of cookies, most browsers allow the visitor to reject cookies. We may share non-Personal Information obtained via cookies with our advertisers and affiliates.

**Clear Gifs  
**We use clear gifs on our websites from Google Analytics and other third party vendors. This enables us to gauge the effectiveness of our services and marketing programs and ad targeting.

**Mobile Device Unique Identifier  
**When you use a mobile device to connect to our websites via a service provider that uniquely identifies your mobile device, we may use this unique identifier to offer you extended services and/or functionality. Certain services may require the collection of your mobile phone number. We may associate that mobile phone number with the mobile device unique identifier. We may also share your mobile phone number with certain select third parties, unless you choose to opt out of such use as described below.

**Physical Location  
**When you download our mobile applications, we may use and store GPS and cell tower information relating to your mobile device, in combination with other location-based information such as your IP address, your billing postal code provided by your carrier, or your registration location, to provide enhanced location-based services, and to serve location-targeted advertising, search results, and other content.

**Disclosure of Information  
**We may share Personal Information with third parties that we engage, and with whom we have written agreements regarding the confidentiality of Personal Information, to help us provide tailored promotions and marketing offers and to improve our digital services, including communications to you via e-mail and mobile telephone, as well as through the Website (“Digital Services”). Other than as set forth above, we will not sell, exchange, rent, lease or otherwise disclose your Personal Information to any third party without your consent. In particular, we do not share Personal Information with third parties for their marketing or promotional use, except as part of a specific program for which you make the choice to participate. For example, we may offer coupons that require you to fill out an advertiser survey in order to be eligible to receive the coupons. We will provide the information to the advertiser, but only when you have chosen to participate. However, Wakefern may disclose Personal Information in special cases: (1) when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to investigate, identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be intentionally or unintentionally: (a) causing injury to Wakefern or to a third party; (b) interfering with the rights of Wakefern or a third party; and/or (c) threatening the physical safety of any person; (2) when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, such as to comply with a court order, subpoena or warrant; (3) to our affiliates; and (4) to any third party who may acquire Wakefern.

**In the Event of Merger, Sale, Acquisition or Change of Control  
**We reserve the right to transfer or assign the Personal Information that we have collected from you in the event of a merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control.

**Procedures to Review Your Personal Information and to Opt-Out  
**You can always contact Wakefern if you wish to review any Personal Information we may have about you. If we have Personal Information about you, we will provide you with a readable copy of such Personal Information at no charge. Factual errors in your Personal Information, including out-of-date information, can be corrected by sending us a request that credibly shows our error. To protect your privacy and security, we take commercially reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access to Personal Information or making corrections.

Also, you may always opt-out of receiving communications from us. If you do not want your Personal Information to be shared with third parties in the manner discussed in this Privacy Policy, please contact Wakefern by using the “Update Your Profile” function in the Price Plus® Club section of the ShopRite® website (https://shopriteforms.mywebgrocer.com/loyalty/LogIn.aspx), by using the “Contact Us” page on this Website, by calling 1-800-SHOPRITE, by visiting the Customer Service Desk in any of our stores, or by writing to the following address:

Wakefern Food Corp.  
Customer Service Department  
P.O. Box 7812 Edison, NJ 08818

If you are receiving e-mail messages from us and do not wish to receive any more, use the links on the bottom of the e-mail message to make changes to your e-mail preferences. If there are no links, follow the instructions at the bottom of the message. When we receive your notification that you want to opt-out, we will process your request as soon as possible. Please note, however, that if you direct us not to share your Personal Information, you may not be eligible for certain ShopRite Price Plus Club promotions that require data about individuals.

**Security of Information  
**The Personal Information collected through the Website is maintained by MyWebGrocer in a manner consistent with current industry standards. Your Personal Information is protected in several ways. Your Personal Information resides on servers that are protected by physical and electronic safeguards. Certain payment information and other Personal Information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) in an effort to prevent unauthorized parties from viewing such information when it is transmitted to us.

In order to most efficiently serve you, credit card transactions are handled by established third-party banking, processing agents and distribution institutions. They receive the information needed to verify and authorize your credit card or other payment information and to process and ship your order. Financial transactions related to your purchases from the Website are handled by clearly identified third parties: please visit their websites to familiarize yourself with their terms and conditions and with their privacy policies. Information relating to your financial transactions will not be maintained on Wakefern servers.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; (b) the security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through the Website cannot be guaranteed; (c) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party; and (d) **WHEN YOU TRANSFER ANY INFORMATION TO US, YOU DO SO AT YOUR OWN RISK. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE AT ALL TIMES FOR MAINTAINING THE CONFIDENTIALITY OF ANY PASSWORD OR OTHER ACCESS INFORMATION.**

 Wakefern agrees to notify individuals of any privacy/data breach when required to do so by law or regulation.

**Links to Third Party Websites  
**The Website may contain links to the websites of third parties not affiliated with Wakefern, including without limitation, Continental Airlines and VeriSign Inc. You understand, acknowledge and agree that these links are provided solely as a convenience to you and not as an endorsement by the Website or Wakefern of the content, advertising or business practices. Wakefern is NOT responsible for the privacy practices or the content on any of these other websites, including any websites that may indicate a special relationship or “partnership” with Wakefern. Wakefern does not disclose unique identifiers to those responsible for the linked websites. The linked websites, however, may collect Personal Information from you when you link to their websites. This collecting of information is not subject to the control of Wakefern. To ensure protection of your privacy, always review the privacy policies of the websites you visit by linking from the Website.

**Third Party Advertisers  
**Third party ad servers or ad networks may display advertisements as part of our Digital Services. These third party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send the advertisements and links that appear on the Website directly to your browser. When you click on the ad, your IP address will be received automatically by the ad server, using technologies that may include cookies, JavaScript and web beacons to personalize the ad content and to evaluate the effectiveness of the ads. Sometimes advertisers are seeking a target audience. For example, an advertiser may ask us to show an ad to users in a particular age group; if you respond to that ad, the ad-server may determine that you are part of the audience they are trying to reach. We recommend that you review the privacy policies of our third party advertisers, for which we are not responsible.

**Wakefern’s Privacy Policy does not apply to, and** **we cannot control the activities of,** **third party advertisers.**

**International Users  
**The Website is hosted in the United States and intended for use in the U.S. If you are accessing the Website from a location outside the U.S. and that location has laws or regulations regarding the collection, use and/or disclosure of Personal Information that is different than U.S. laws and regulations, please be advised that your continued use of the Website, which is governed by U.S. law (as stated in the Terms & Conditions), indicates your consent to the transfer of your Personal Information to the U.S.

Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. We never collect or maintain information at the Website from persons we know to be under age 13. Please do not communicate with or contact us if you are under age 13. By your participation in our Website activities, you certify that you are at least 13 years of age and meet all other eligibility requirements of the Website. If we learn that Personal Information relating to someone under the age of 13 has been collected on the Website, we will take appropriate steps to delete such information.

Changes to this Privacy Policy Wakefern may revise this Privacy Policy over time as new features are added to the Website or as Internet law and standards evolve, and this will be reflected by the “Last Modified” notice below. We will post those changes prominently but we do recommend that you read this Privacy Policy periodically when you visit the Website. Changes will not apply retroactively to Personal Information that was collected before the changes to the Privacy Policy,except as may be required by law.

Last Modified: May 10, 2013
